University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1966-2006; 3; 3.5 cubic ft.
  - 9900-03 Undergraduate Academic Council Revision of the General Education Requirements Approved 12-06-99, 1999-2000 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 9900-01R Undergraduate Academic Council Resolution Concerning Freshman Writing Approved 12-16-99, 1999-2000 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 9900-02R Undergraduate Academic Council Resolution Concerning the Quality of General Education Approved 12-16-99, 1999-2000 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 9900-04 Undergraduate Academic Council Revision of Procedures for Undergraduate Withdrawals from the University Approved 03-03-00, 1999-2000 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 9900-05 Postmatriculation Transfer Credit with Grade of 0 Approved 03-03-00, 1999-2000 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Summary of Legislation, 2000-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - Summary of Legislation, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 0001-01 Partnership Agreement for the Establishment of Army Reserve Officer's Training (ROTC) Instruction at the Unlversity at Aibany EPC Approved 02-27-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 0001-02 University at Albany Policy for the Responsible Use of Information Technology -- LISC Approved 02-27-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 0001-01R Resolution for Conslderation by the University Senate, Unieersity at Albany, On the Implementatlon of General Education Programs University Senate Executive Committee Approved 02-12-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 0001-03 Undergraduate Academic Council Proposal to Establish an Interdisciplinary Undergraduate Major in International Studies Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 0001-04 Undergraduate Academic Council The New General Education Program Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 0001-05 Proposal to Change Graduate Academic Policies Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 0001-06 Graduate Academic Council Proposal to Establish an Interdisciplinary Graduate Certificate in Nonprofit Management and Leadership Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 0001-07 Undergraduate Academic Council and Graduate Academic Council Joint Bachelors/Masters Programs Linking the M.S. in Health Policy and Management with Undergraduate Programs in Psychology (B.A.), Sociology (S.A.), and Economics (B.A. and B.S.) Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 0001-08 Undergraduate Academic Council Curricular Revision from the School of Education Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 0001-09 Undergraduate Academic Council Proposed Faculty-Initiated lnterdisciplinary Minor in Bioethics Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 0001-10 ULC Principles for a Just Community Changes Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - Summary of Legislation, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 0102 -01 Graduate Academic Council Proposal to Change Graduate Academic Policy Pertaining to Leave of Absence from a Doctoral Program Approved 10-26-01, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-02 Undergraduate Academic Council Revision of the Undergraduate "New General Education Program" Implementation Dates for Transfers Approved 2-7 -02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-03 Undergraduate Academic Council Revision of the Undergraduate Residence Requirements Approval 2-7 -02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-04 Undergraduate Academic Council & Graduate Academic Council Proposal to Establish a Joint Degree Involving the BA in Public Policy and the Master's Degree in Public Administration (MPA), 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-05 Proposed Amendment A to Senate Bill No. 0001-02 (University at Albany Policy for the Responsible Use of Information Technology Approved 11-19-01, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-06 Graduate Academic Council MS in Literacy and Special Education Approval 2-20-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-07 Undergraduate Academic Council General Education Program Assessment Plan Approval 4-16-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-08 Undergraduate Academic Council Syllabus Requirements for Undergraduate Courses Approval 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-09 Undergraduate Academic Council Unresolved Grades at Graduation Approval 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-10 Undergraduate Academic Council Undergraduate Multiple Majors & Minors Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-11 Undergraduate Academic Council Forensic Chemistry Track in the Major Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-12 Undergraduate Academic Council Faculty-Initiated Interdiscipllnary Major in Environmental Science Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-13 Graduate Academic Council Joint Master of Arts in History (MA) and Master of Arts In Public Policy (MPP) Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-14 Conversion of Dual Degree Programs: BA or BS/MLS to BA or BS/MSLS, MA/MLS to MA/MSIS Historyor English Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-15 Combined BA/MA in Women's Studies Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-16 [record missing], 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - 0102-17 Proposed Amendment A (LISC) Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - Summary of Legislation, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - 0203-01R Resolution, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-02R General Education Resolution, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-01 Graduate Academic Council Graduate Certificate in Autism Approved 10-25-02, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-02 Changes in the Actuarial Program (Undergraduate Academic Council) Approved 12-13-02, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-03 Proposal to Establish Graduate Degree Programs (Ph.D. & M.S.) in NanoSciences and NanoEngineering (Grauduate Academic Council) Approved 12-13-02, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-04 Recommendations and Policy Framework on Responding to Misconduct in Research and Scholarship (Epc, RES, CAFE) Approved 04-30-02, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-05 Modification of Starting Times for Courses Meeting in Standard Time Zones (EPC) Approved 5-15-03, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-06 Majors in East Asian Studies and Japanese Studies (UAC,EPC) Approved 5-15-03, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-07 BA in Political Science / MA in Public Affairs and Po1icy (Undergraduate Academic Council, Graduate Academic Council) Approved 5-14-03, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-08 Proposal to Establish a Master of Science Degree Program in Forensic Biology (GAC) Approved 5-15-03, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-09 Human Biology Major (Undergraduate Academic Council, EPC) Approved 5-14-03, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-10 Procedures for Resolving Academic Grievances (Undergraduate Academic Council, Graduate Academic Council) Approved 5-15-03, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-11 Revision to the "Last Day for Undergraduates to Drop a Course" (Undergraduate Academic Council) Approved 5-15-03, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-12 Changes in Policy on Faculty Eligibility to Teach Graduate Courses (Graduate Academic Council) Approved 5-15-03, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 0203-13 Suspension of Classes on Fountain Day (SAC, ULC) Approved 6-10-03, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - Summary of Legislation, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - 0304-01R Resolution-President Hitchcock. Introduced by Current and Past Senate Chairs Approved 10-27-03, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-02R Resolution for Recognition of SUNY Albany Peace and Justice. Presented by Professors Seidrnan, Cable, Benjamin and Wittner Approved 11-03-03, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-03R Resolution on Presidential Search Committee Approved 11-03-03, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-04R College of Nanoscale Science and Engineering and Integrated University Govemance. Introduced by Current and Past Senate Chairs Approved 03-15-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-05R University at Albany Resolution on General Education Assessment Approved 04-19-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-06R Albany Faculty Action Needed to Secure Access to Journals at Affordable Price for SUNY Faculty & Students (LISC) Approved 05-03-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-07R Pedestrian Issues (ULC) Approved 05-03-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-08R Resolution to affirm and uphold civil rights and civil liberties at the University at Albany Approved 05-03-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-01 Faculty ByLaws Amendments Approved 01-08-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-02 Faculty ByLaws Amendment for Part Time Representation Approved 01-08-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-03 Senate Charter Approved 01-08-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-04 Revision of semester withdrawal deadline for students having less than a 2.0 cumulative grade point average (Undegraduate Academic Council) Approved 11-26-03, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-05 Revisions within the General Education Program (Undergraduate Academic Council) Approved 11-26-03, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-06 Revisions in policies governing excuses from undergraduate classes, exams, and timely completion of assignments (Undergraduate Academic Council) Approved 11-26-03, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-07 Proposal to establish a Graduate Certificate Program in Public Health - Fundamentals & Principles (Graduate Academic Council & EPC) Approved 12-18-03, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-08 Formal Elimination ofthe General Education Honors Program (Undergraduate Academic Council) Approved 01-05-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-09 Revision of the Criteria for Dean's List and Dean's Commendation for Part-Time Students (Undergraduate Academic Council) Approved 01-05-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-10 Merger of Two Departments in the School of Public Health (EPC) Approved 02-12-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-11 Revisions ofthe Undergraduate English Major (Undergraduate Academic Council) Approved 03-15-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-12 Revision of "Oral Discourse" General Education Criteria (Undergraduate Academic Council) Approved 03-15-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-13 ROTC and Applied Elective Credit (Undergraduate Academic Council) Appproved 03-15-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-14 Revision ofUndergraduate Admissions Policies (Undergraduate Academic Council) Appproved 03-15-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-15 Administrative Support for the University Senate (Govemance Subcommittee) Appproved 03-15-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-16 Departmental Name Change within the School of Business (EPC) Appproved 03-19-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-17 Proposal to Amend the Charter of the University Senate, SX.4.6 Graduate Academic Council (Graduate Academic Council) Approved 05-05-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-18 Proposal to Discontinue the Doctor of Arts Program in Humanistic Studies (EPC & Graduate Academic Council) Approved 05-05-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-19 Proposal to Establish a Jointly Registered Dual Degree Program, M.A. (public Affairs and Policy)-UAlbany / J.D. (Law)-Albany Law SchooI (Graduate Academic Council) Approved 05-05-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-20 Additional Membership on Councils and Committees (Governance Subcommittee) Approved 05-05-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-21 Proposal to Establish a Registered Dual Degree Program M.S.W./M.A. Public Affairs & Policy (Graduate Academic Council) Approved 05-05-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-22 Proposal to Establish a Jointly Registered Dual Degree Program, M.S.W.-UAlbany/M.S. Bioethics-Albany Medical College and Graduate College of Union University (Graduate Academic Council) Approved 05-05-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-23 Revisions of Undergraduate Programs in "Earth Science" and "History Social Studies" (Undegraduate Academic Council) Approved 05-05-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-24 Campus Distribution Policy for Newspapers and Other News Periodicals (CAFE) Approved 05-03-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-25 Campus Policy on Freedom of Expression (CAFE) Approved 05-03-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-26 Definitions ofUndergraduate Credit (Undegraduate Academic Council) Approved 06-17-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-27 Proposal to Establish a Master of Science (M.S.) Program in Applied Chemistry (Graduate Academic Council) Approved 06-17-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-28 Suspension of Classes in Recognition of and Respect for Muslim Religious Holidays (ULC) (Retumed to COUllcil, not passed) Approved 05-03-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 0304-29 Dissolution of the Department of Classics (EPC) Approved 06-17-04, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - Summary of Legislation, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 0405-1R Resolution Endorsing the MOU with CNSE Approved 12-06-04, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-01 UPC - Additonal Membership on Council and Committees Approved 11-04-04, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-02 CERS - University at Albany Policy and Procedures on Misconduct in Research and Scholarship Approved 02-17-05, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-03 Undergraduate Academic Council - Revision of the Senate Chapter Regarding Undergraduate Academic Council Membership Approved 11-04-04, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-04 Undergraduate Academic Council - Elimination of the Pre-Fall 2000 General Education Program Approved 11-04-04, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-05, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-06, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-07, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-08, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-09, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-10, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-11, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-12, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-13, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-14, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-15, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-16, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-17, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-18, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-19, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-20, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-21, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-22, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-23, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-24, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-25, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-26, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-27, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-28, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-29, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - 0405-30, 2004-2005 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Summary of Legislation, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 0506-01R Senate: Resolution to Recognize Jayne Vandenburgh for her Exemplary Service to the Senate Approved 09-12-05, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-02R EC: Resolution in Support of the New York State College of Ceramics Approved 11-21-05, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-03R EC: Resolution opposing the "Academic Bill of Rights" Approved 12-19-05, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-04R ULC: Resolution for Position for Intramurals and Recreational. Activities. Approved 05-15-06, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-05R ULC: Resolution for a University at Alany Family Leave Policy Approved 05-15-06, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-01, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-02, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-03, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-04, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-05, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-06, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-07, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - 0506-08, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-09, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-10, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-11, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-12, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-13, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-14, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-15, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-16, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-17, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-18, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0506-19, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0506-20, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0506-21, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0506-22, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0506-23, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0506-24, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0506-25, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0506-26, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0506-27, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0506-01, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0506-02, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0506-03, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0506-04, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - 0506-05, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - 0506-06, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - 0506-07, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - 0506-08, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - 0506-09, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - 0506-10, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - 0506-11, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 0506-12, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 0506-13, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 0506-14, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 0506-15, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 0506-16, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 0506-17, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 0506-18, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 0506-19, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 0506-20, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - 0506-21, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 0506-22, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 0506-23, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 0506-24, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 0506-25, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 0506-26, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 0506-27, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 0506 Resolution 1, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 0506 Resolution 2, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 0506 Resolution 3, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - 0506 Resolution 4, 2005-2006 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - Summary of Legislation, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - 0607-01, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-02, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-03, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-04, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-05, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-06, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-07, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-08, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-09, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-10, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-11, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-12, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-13, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-14, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-15, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-16, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607-17, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607 Resolution 1, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607 Resolution 2, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607 Resolution 3, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - 0607 Legislation - extra photocopies, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - Summary of Legislation, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 0708 Resolution 1, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708 Resolution 2, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708 Resolution 3, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-01, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-02, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-03, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-04, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-05, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-06, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-07, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-08, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-09, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-10, 2007-2008 (Box 4 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 0708-11, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-12, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-13, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-14, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-15, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-16, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-17, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-18, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-19, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-20, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-21, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - 0708-22, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0708-23, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0708-24, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0708-25, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - 0708-26, 2007-2008 (Box 5 (3-Legislation), Folder 2)